Guide to the Vassar College Alumnae/i Biographical Files (AAVC), circa 1865-2015
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Class of 1920
  - Guibord, Ruth L. (Box 56)
  - Guild, Harriet G. (Box 56)
  - Gutwillig, Mildred A. (Box 57)
  - Hadley, Laura B. (Box 57)
  - Hadsell, Susan P. (Box 57)
  - Haight, Dorothy M. (Box 57)
  - Hale, Lucy D. (Box 57)
  - Harmon, Frances A. (Box 57)
  - Harper, Mary L. (Box 57)
  - Harrington, Ruth (Box 57)
  - Harris, Eleanor B. (Box 57)
  - Harrison, Geneva W. (Box 57)
  - Harvey, Grace F. (Box 57)
  - Hawkins, Clara S. (Box 57)
  - Henderson, Marjorie (Box 57)
  - Hodge, Genevieve A. (Box 57)
  - Hogsett, Elizabeth (Box 57)
  - Holden, Persis S. (Box 57)
  - Hubbard, Elizabeth C. (Box 57)
  - Hurlbutt, Cornelia Moen (Box 57)
  - Hyman, Natalie S. (Box 57)
  - Jackson, Frances M. (Box 57)
  - Jackson, Helen E. (Box 57)
  - Johnson, Dorothy B. (Box 57)
  - Johnson, Janet G. (Box 57)
  - Jones, Catherine H. (Box 57)
  - Justin, Eleanore R. (Box 57)
  - Kendall, Katherine (Box 57)
  - Kendrick, Jean (Box 57)
  - Kennan, Constance L. (Box 57)
  - Kerr, Marjorie E. (Box 57)
  - Kilham, Teresa (Box 57)
  - Kissam, Eleanor (Box 57)
  - Knapp, Valeria A. (Box 57)
  - Kroeger, Eleanor A. (Box 57)
  - Krolik, Hortense (Box 57)
  - Kuh, Helen M. (Box 57)
  - Kush, Gertrude E. (Box 57)
  - Lambert, Anne R. (Box 57)
  - Landman, Helen (Box 57)
  - Lane, Cherry (Box 57)
  - Langthorn, Elizabeth C. (Box 57)
  - Latham, Mary (Box 57)
  - Lawshe, Harriet (Box 57)
  - Lechtman, Miriam (Box 57)
  - Lee, Katherine E. (Box 57)
  - Leonard, Dorothy S. (Box 57)
  - Levey, Edna M. (Box 57)
  - Lewis, Helen T. (Box 57)
  - Lichty, M Dorothy (Box 57)
  - Liggett, Frances B. (Box 57)
  - Lillie, Catherine C. (Box 57)
  - Lindsay, Janet E. (Box 57)
  - Linington, Sarah S. (Box 57)
  - Litchfield, Ethel C. (Box 57)
  - Livingston, Therese R. (Box 57)
  - Lowenthal, Ilona M. (Box 57)
  - Lowinson, Adele (Box 57)
  - Lyon, Carolyn (Box 57)
  - Macaulay, Jean A. (Box 57)
  - MacGowan, Helen R. (Box 57)
  - MacGowan, M Todd (Box 57)
  - MacLeish, Ishbel M. (Box 57)
  - MacRae, Agnes (Box 57)
  - Mahoney, M Dorothy (Box 57)
  - Marburg, Clara (Box 57)
  - Marshall, Elizabeth W. (Box 57)
  - Martin, Lucille (Box 57)
  - Martin, Marjory A. (Box 57)
  - Martin, Mary A. (Box 57)
  - Mathews, Helen (Box 57)
  - Mattison, Marjorie G. (Box 57)
  - Mattoon, Lois (Box 57)
  - Mayer, Erna H. (Box 57)
  - McAfee, Mildred H. (Box 57)
  - McAndrew, Marjorie (Box 57)
  - McBrier, Geraldine E. (Box 57)
  - McCarson, Eleanor (Box 57)
  - McConway, Isabel L. (Box 57)
  - McFarland, Elzamarie (Box 57)
  - McKinstry, Ruth F. (Box 57)
  - McKittrick, Mary (Box 57)
  - Meigs, Lucia L. (Box 57)
  - Meldrum, Gladys H. (Box 57)
  - Miles, Elizabeth (Box 57)
  - Miller, Dorothea K. (Box 57)
  - Miller, Harriet H. (Box 57)
  - Miller, Helen T. (Box 57)
  - Miller, Mildred (Box 57)
  - Miner, Mary (Box 57)
  - Miner, Margaret M. (Box 57)
  - Morris, Adaline (Box 57)
  - Morris, Eugenia R. (Box 57)
  - Morse, Marion E. (Box 57)
  - Morton, Helen (Box 57)
  - Mott, Katharine (Box 57)
  - Moulton, Doris S. (Box 57)
  - Muir, Kathleen B. (Box 57)
  - Nesmith, Katharine B. (Box 57)
  - Nielsen, Florence P. (Box 57)
  - Northrup, Marty W. (Box 57)
  - Oliver, Brenda I. (Box 57)
  - Otto, Elsa L. (Box 57)
  - Page, Edith N. (Box 57)
  - Pardee, Charlotte C. (Box 57)
  - Parsons, Eleanor M. (Box 57)
  - Pennock, Marian (Box 57)
  - Plum, Margaret H. (Box 58)
  - Pond, Ruth (Box 58)
  - Potter, Caroline (Box 58)
  - Potter, Mabel (Box 58)
  - Pratt, Margaret (Box 58)
  - Prendergast, Eleanor (Box 58)
  - Prentiss, Dorothy L. (Box 58)
  - Quintus, Katrina (Box 58)
  - Ratcliffe, Marion L. (Box 58)
  - Reed, Margaret C. (Box 58)
  - Regensberg, Jeanette (Box 58)
  - Reinmund, Dorothy (Box 58)
  - Remer, Virginia B. (Box 58)
  - Reynolds, Margaret V. (Box 58)
  - Ridenour, Ruth B. (Box 58)
  - Rockwell, Janet K. (Box 58)
  - Rodgers, Margaret A. (Box 58)
  - Rohn, Margaret L. (Box 58)
  - Rolfe, Dorothy S. (Box 58)
  - Romeyn, Barbara (Box 58)
  - Russell, Elizabeth O. (Box 58)
  - Russell, Helma C. (Box 58)
  - Rust, Marjorie L. (Box 58)
  - Rutty, E Maud (Box 58)
  - Ryrie, Margaret (Box 58)
  - Sague, Katherine N. (Box 58)
  - Savery, Esther (Box 58)
  - Schatz, Ernestine E. (Box 58)
  - Schickle, Gretchen (Box 58)
  - Schulman, Lavinia D. (Box 58)
  - Scott, Margaret L. (Box 58)
  - Searles, Ruth W. (Box 58)
  - Sedgwick, Ruth (Box 58)
  - Seitner, Henrietta (Box 58)
  - Seymour, Jane (Box 58)
  - Shattuck, Mary B. (Box 58)
  - Tsa, Sieu-Tsu (Box 58)
  - Simpson, Isobel B. (Box 58)
  - Simpson, Ruth (Box 58)
  - Smith, Laura H. (Box 58)
  - Smith, Muriel E. (Box 58)
  - Snydacker, Clara (Box 58)
  - Springer, Cornelia B. (Box 58)
  - Stark, Olive Beatrice (Box 58)
  - Steers, Mildred E. (Box 58)
  - Stevens, Pauline H. (Box 58)
  - Stoddart, Gertrude E. (Box 58)
  - Strittmatter, Barbara (Box 58)
  - Swain, Barbara (Box 58)
  - Tallman, Esther J (Box 58)
  - Tennant, Katharine V. (Box 58)
  - Thayer, Marion A. (Box 58)
  - Thomas, Beatrice L. (Box 58)
  - Thomas, Marjorie B. (Box 58)
  - Thompson, Hazel M. (Box 58)
  - Tippy, Helen W. (Box 58)
  - Townsend, Elizabeth (Box 58)
  - Treat, Katharine V. (Box 58)
  - Trimble, Laura (Box 58)
  - Troy, Almira L. (Box 58)
  - Valentine, Louise H. (Box 58)
  - Van Dervoort, Esther M. (Box 58)
  - Van Evera, Katharine (Box 58)
  - Van Siclen, Matilda (Box 58)
  - Van Tuyl, Katharine (Box 58)
  - Van Vilet, Barbara H. (Box 58)
  - Vanderpool, Hilda E. (Box 58)
  - Vassar, Helen E. (Box 58)
  - Voorhees, Ruth S. (Box 58)
  - Wallace, Mary O. (Box 58)
  - Walling, Marietta M. (Box 58)
  - Walworth, Dorothy (Box 58)
  - Ware, Caroline F. (Box 58)
  - Waterman, Katherine (Box 58)
  - Weber, Ruth A. (Box 58)
  - Weed, Eleanor H. (Box 58)
  - Weil, Gladys (Box 58)
  - Weis, Isabel G. (Box 58)
  - Werntz, Mildred (Box 58)
  - Westcott, Lilian V. (Box 58)
  - Wheeler, Elizabeth Y. (Box 58)
  - Wheeler, Helen L. (Box 58)
  - White, Clarissa D. (Box 58)
  - Whiting, Frances L. (Box 58)
  - Wickham, Dorothea E. (Box 58)
  - Wilcox, Kathryn C. (Box 58)
  - Wiley, Cynthia E. (Box 58)
  - Williams, Catherine J (Box 58)
  - Wilner, Margia C. (Box 58)
  - Wilson, Helen A. (Box 58)
  - Winne, Adelaide (Box 58)
  - Witham, Anne W. (Box 58)
  - Witte, Jeannette T. (Box 58)
  - Wollaeger, Gertrude E. (Box 58)
  - Woods, Mary C. (Box 58)
  - Woodworth, Marjorie (Box 58)
  - York, Cynthia M. (Box 58)
  - Young, Alyse P. (Box 58)
- Class of 1921
  - Abbott, Elizabeth T. (Box 59)
  - Allen, Ruth P. (Box 59)
  - Allport, Katherine M. (Box 59)
  - Ambrose, Elizabeth (Box 59)
  - Ames, Catherine G. (Box 59)
  - Anderson, Dorothy M. (Box 59)
  - Anderson, Frances B. (Box 59)
  - Andrews, Roslyn W. (Box 59)
  - Ault, Edith D. (Box 59)
  - Averbeck, Carolyn R. (Box 59)
  - Babcock, Heath (Box 59)
  - Bailey, Carolyn S. (Box 59)
  - Ball, Charlotte W. (Box 59)
  - Barber, Margaret A. (Box 59)
  - Barck, Dorothy C. (Box 59)
  - Barker, Helen J. (Box 59)
  - Barnes, Gertrude M. (Box 59)
  - Bartlett, M. Janet (Box 59)
  - Baumann, Eleanore, O. (Box 59)
  - Beale, Mary (Box 59)
  - Beecher, Aroline A. (Box 59)
  - Bennet, Sarah A. (Box 59)
  - Bennett, Helen R. (Box 59)
  - Benshimol, Harriet (Box 59)
  - Biddle, Mary H. (Box 59)
  - Bird, Beatrice T. (Box 59)
  - Bishop, H. Miriam (Box 59)
  - Bixby, Katharine (Box 59)
  - Black, Antoinette G. (Box 59)
  - Bolton, Audrey B. (Box 59)
  - Boothman, Margaret (Box 59)
  - Bosley, Ruth W. (Box 59)
  - Bovaird, Cecily J. (Box 59)
  - Boyd, Lois J. (Box 59)
  - Boynton, Margaret B. (Box 59)
  - Brantingham, Helen L. (Box 59)
  - Brill, Marian E. (Box 59)
  - Brodek, Edith J. (Box 59)
  - Brown, Ina M. (Box 59)
  - Brownell, Gertrude L. (Box 59)
  - Brush, Marjorie J. (Box 59)
  - Buckbee, Frances C. (Box 59)
  - Buckbee, Mary F. (Box 59)
  - Buckland, Julia T. (Box 59)
  - Buffum, Mary F. (Box 59)
  - Bullitt, Martha D. (Box 59)
  - Bultman, Anna (Box 59)
  - Bultman, Wilhelmine (Box 59)
  - Burke, Emily T. (Box 59)
  - Burnet, Katharine K. (Box 59)
  - Burnham, Helen P. (Box 59)
  - Burton, Sara F. (Box 59)
  - Butler, Barbara, L. (Box 59)
  - Butler, Lucy (Box 59)
  - Cahill, Marion C. (Box 59)
  - Callow, Frances M. (Box 59)
  - Cambron, Carroll E. (Box 59)
  - Carlat, Anna (Box 59)
  - Carter, Elizabeth C. (Box 59)
  - Carter, Laura H. (Box 59)
  - Carter Rebecca B. (Box 59)
  - Caughey, Mary L. (Box 59)
  - Chambers, Thalia L. (Box 59)
  - Cheney, Clara F. (Box 59)
  - Child, Margaret S. (Box 59)
  - Cobb, Emily L. (Box 59)
  - Colfelt, Natalye (Box 59)
  - Corbin, Elinor (Box 59)
  - Cornwell, Hazel J. (Box 59)
  - Cotton, Alma L. (Box 59)
  - Cox, Katharine C. (Box 59)
  - Cox, Mildred V. (Box 59)
  - Craft, Marian H. (Box 59)
  - Craighead, Julia H. (Box 59)
  - Crooks, Helene M. (Box 59)
  - Dallmeyer, Katrine (Box 59)
  - Davis, Georgene W. (Box 59)
  - Davis, Jean (Box 59)
  - Davison, Amy D. (Box 59)
  - Day, Dorothy J. (Box 59)
  - DeBevoise, Winifred G. (Box 59)
  - De Golier, Eleanor (Box 59)
  - Denton, Elsie M. (Box 59)
  - DePuy, Louise (Box 59)
  - Deuel, Eleanor (Box 59)
  - Dickenson, Vivien (Box 59)
  - Dillingham, Pauline B. (Box 59)
  - Dixon, Evalyn E. (Box 59)
  - Dunn, Winifred W. (Box 59)
  - Dwight, Elizabeth P. (Box 59)
  - Dwight, Laura S. (Box 59)
  - Dykes, Dorothy (Box 59)
  - Edwards, Elizabeth S. (Box 59)
  - Eisendrath, Edith (Box 59)
  - Elias, Ethel M. (Box 59)
  - Ewing, E. Eileen (Box 59)
  - Ewing, Marjorie R. (Box 59)
  - Fearn, Carol G. (Box 59)
  - Fellheimer, Jeannette (Box 59)
  - Fenn, Martha W. (Box 59)
  - Fenstermaker, Grace E. (Box 59)
  - Fenton, Frances B. (Box 59)
  - Field, Isabel S. (Box 59)
  - Finch, Mildred M. (Box 59)
  - Fitts, Margaret M. (Box 59)
  - Flanders, Evelyn H. (Box 59)
  - Ford, Florence L. (Box 59)
  - Ford, Marguerite S. (Box 59)
  - France, Helen H. (Box 59)
  - Fraser, Ruth B. (Box 59)
  - Free, G. Lucile (Box 59)
  - Frenning, Frances E. (Box 59)
  - Fuld, Hortense S. (Box 59)
  - Gallagher, Emily (Box 59)
  - Goldin, Frances (Box 59)
  - Gordon, Virginia S. (Box 59)
  - Goss, Anne (Box 59)
  - Greenshaw, Ursula A. (Box 59)
  - Griffin, Helen (Box 59)
  - Grimes, Isabel (Box 59)
  - Gruener, Katharine E. (Box 59)
  - Haaf, Therese (Box 59)
  - Hague, Miriam (Box 59)
  - Haines, Sarah R. (Box 59)
  - Hall, Catharyn S. (Box 59)
  - Hall, Marie M. (Box 59)
  - Hallett, Dorothy (Box 59)
  - Handy, Rebecca M. (Box 59)
  - Hansen, Esther V. (Box 59)
  - Hartshorne, Emily B. (Box 59)
  - Hawkes, Evelyn E. (Box 59)
  - Haywood, Katherine E. (Box 59)
  - Haiman, Helen (Box 59)
  - Heath, Margaret W. (Box 60)
  - Hedrick, Anna F. (Box 60)
  - Hellyer, Anna F. (Box 60)
  - Henn, Jeannette M. (Box 60)
  - Henry, Mary (Box 60)
  - Hersloff, Harriet (Box 60)
  - Hesse, Margot P. (Box 60)
  - Hewitt, Helen M. (Box 60)
  - Hewson, Louise R. (Box 60)
  - Hill, Margaret (Box 60)
  - Histed, Katharine R. (Box 60)
  - Hitchcock, Hilda (Box 60)
  - Hixon, Virginia (Box 60)
  - Holley, Margaret S. (Box 60)
  - Hollis, Elinor V. (Box 60)
  - Hood, Charlotte F. (Box 60)
  - Hooker, Emily H. (Box 60)
  - Howland, Marjory (Box 60)
  - Hubbell, Elizabeth (Box 60)
  - Hubbell, Margaret (Box 60)
  - Hubbs, Evelyn (Box 60)
  - Hulsapple, Alma E. (Box 60)
  - Humason, Sarah W. (Box 60)
  - Hunter, Amy L. (Box 60)
  - Hurlock, Dorothy C. (Box 60)
  - Ickler, Dorothy S. (Box 60)
  - Indahl, Solveig (Box 60)
  - Ingalls, Helena M. (Box 60)
  - Inglis, Agnes K. (Box 60)
  - Jennings, Eva L. (Box 60)
  - Johnson, Ella G. (Box 60)
  - Johnson, Margaret (Box 60)
  - Johnson, Mary Dudley (Box 60)
  - Jones, Alison (Box 60)
  - Jones, Elizabeth T. (Box 60)
  - Jones, Ethel B. (Box 60)
  - Jones, Helen E. (Box 60)
  - Kahn, Lydia (Box 60)
  - Kahn, Vera (Box 60)
  - Kattwinkel, Irene (Box 60)
  - Katz, Esther (Box 60)
  - Kaufmann, Lucy (Box 60)
  - Keith, Marion A. (Box 60)
  - Kellemen, Harriet C. (Box 60)
  - Kinley, Harriet L. (Box 60)
  - Knapp, Frances H. (Box 60)
  - Knott, Edith S. (Box 60)
  - Kuhn, Agnes E. (Box 60)
  - Kummer, Roblen M. (Box 60)
  - Langdon, Myra E. (Box 60)
  - Larsen, Elizabeth A. (Box 60)
  - Leith, Isabella M. (Box 60)
  - Lester, Katharine M. (Box 60)
  - Lewis, Carmalita (Box 60)
  - Lewis, Marion M. (Box 60)
  - Lewis, Winifred K. (Box 60)
  - Lloyd, Elizabeth (Box 60)
  - Lowman, Edith C. (Box 60)
  - MacDonald, Margaret T. (Box 60)
  - MacGregor, Catherine S. (Box 60)
  - Maguire, Margaret R. (Box 60)
  - Marburg, Anita (Box 60)
  - Mason, Marion L. (Box 60)
  - Masson, Katherine M. (Box 60)
  - Mayo, Amanda M. (Box 60)
  - McClintock, E. Gertrude (Box 60)
  - McCormick, Katherine (Box 60)
  - McKenzie, Dorothy G. (Box 60)
  - McKinney, Frances R. (Box 60)
  - McMahon, Margaret (Box 60)
  - Mead, Theodora (Box 60)
  - Meiser, Edith M. (Box 60)
  - Millay, Kathleen, K. (Box 60)
  - Miller, Antha (Box 60)
  - Mitchell, Carol L. (Box 60)
  - Mohn, Elizabeth A. (Box 60)
  - Moss, Winifred (Box 60)
  - Murphey, M. Josephine (Box 60)
  - Newcomet, Elizabeth M. (Box 60)
  - Northrup, Louise (Box 60)
  - Noyes, Natalie V. (Box 60)
  - Nulsen, Elizabeth J. (Box 60)
  - Otter, Melville, W. (Box 60)
  - Parks, Hester (Box 60)
  - Partridge, Elizabeth W. (Box 60)
  - Passano, Elizabeth W. (Box 60)
  - Paull, Anna L. (Box 60)
  - Peck, E. Gertrude (Box 60)
  - Pegram, Mercy R. (Box 60)
  - Pendreigh, Edith F. (Box 60)
  - Pfund, Marion C. (Box 60)
  - Pierson, Margaret B. (Box 60)
  - Pommier, Andree M. (Box 60)
  - Poole, Phebe (Box 60)
  - Prentice, Anna (Box 60)
  - Price, Grace M. (Box 60)
  - Quigley, Henrietta (Box 60)
  - Richardson, Eleanor K. (Box 60)
  - Rickard, Antoinette (Box 60)
  - Robbins, Helen C. (Box 60)
  - Robinson, Catherine M. (Box 60)
  - Rogers, Florence (Box 60)
  - Rood, Harriet E. (Box 60)
  - Rose, Marian F. (Box 60)
  - Rosenfeld, Elizabeth (Box 60)
  - Ross, Alice J. (Box 60)
  - Ross, Margaret B. (Box 60)
  - Roth, Eugenia (Box 60)
  - Rudolph, Isabelle W. (Box 60)
  - Ruml, Frances (Box 60)
  - Russell, Constance L. (Box 60)
  - Russell, Louise T. (Box 60)
  - Russell, Margaret E. (Box 60)
  - Rutherford, Sarah C. (Box 60)
  - Sagendorph, Frances C. (Box 60)
  - Sandford, Saidee R. (Box 60)
  - Sasse, Hannah (Box 60)
  - Schmalz, Madeleine R. (Box 60)
  - Schmidt, Dorothea (Box 60)
  - Schneider, Jean (Box 60)
  - Schoeneweiss, Louise (Box 60)
  - Schulz, Marie (Box 60)
  - Scudder, Dorothy O. (Box 60)
  - Searle, Margaret (Box 60)
  - Sellers, Clifford W. (Box 60)
  - Shaw, Kathryn A. (Box 60)
  - Smeltzer, Airy E. (Box 60)
  - Smith, Margaret C. (Box 60)
  - Spanhoofd, Wilhelmina W. (Box 60)
  - St. Clair, Harriet W. (Box 60)
  - Stadlinger, Helene L. (Box 60)
  - Starr, Catherine (Box 60)
  - Stehn, Katharine H. (Box 60)
  - Steiger, Katherine P. (Box 60)
  - Stephenson, Katrina S. (Box 60)
  - Sternberg, Ruth M. (Box 60)
  - Stevens, Adelia R. (Box 60)
  - Stillman, Margaret H. (Box 60)
  - Taylor, Harriett E. (Box 60)
  - Thomas, Katheryne C. (Box 60)
  - Thompson, Doris (Box 60)
  - Thompson, Dorothy (Box 60)
  - Thompson, Inez S. (Box 60)
  - Tichenor, Virginia P. (Box 60)
  - Todd, Dorothy L. (Box 60)
  - Travell, Margaret H. (Box 60)
  - Treat, Frances (Box 60)
  - Trevor, Katherine (Box 60)
  - Trowbridge, Alice (Box 60)
  - Turnbull, L. Minerva (Box 60)
  - Ullman, Carolyn M. (Box 60)
  - Ulrich, Elizabeth A. (Box 60)
  - Unzicker, Anna L. (Box 60)
  - Van Alstyne, Dorothy (Box 60)
  - Van Cleve, Lillian B. (Box 60)
  - Van Kirk, Frances S. (Box 60)
  - Vannier, Edna N. (Box 60)
  - Varney, Constance (Box 60)
  - Wade, Helen L. (Box 61)
  - Wade, Leila R. (Box 61)
  - Wagner, Gladys I. (Box 61)
  - Walker, Carolyn (Box 61)
  - Wallace, Virginia G. (Box 61)
  - Walton, E. Tess (Box 61)
  - Ward, Marjorie S. (Box 61)
  - Watt, Jacksonia (Box 61)
  - Webb, Harriet M. (Box 61)
  - Webber, Elizabeth (Box 61)
  - Weed, Anne A. (Box 61)
  - Welborn, Mary C. (Box 61)
  - Welch, Emily W. (Box 61)
  - Wells, Eleanor O. (Box 61)
  - West, Emily L. (Box 61)
  - West, Mary I. (Box 61)
  - Wetherby, Esther S. (Box 61)
  - White, Mary W. (Box 61)
  - Whitehead, Marguerite (Box 61)
  - Whitmore, Helen I. (Box 61)
  - Wiener, Margaret (Box 61)
  - Wile, Leah B. (Box 61)
  - Wilkinson, Anne B. (Box 61)
  - Williams, A. Clae (Box 61)
  - Williams, Elinor F. (Box 61)
  - Williamson, Marjorie (Box 61)
  - Wilson, Leisa G. (Box 61)
  - Winslow, Constance S. (Box 61)
  - Wolf, Ruth H. (Box 61)
  - Wood, Phebe (Box 61)
  - Wood, Priscilla A. (Box 61)
  - Woods, Mary T. (Box 61)
- Class of 1922
  - Abbott, Joan (Box 61)
  - Agostini, Amelia (Box 61)
  - Alexander, Jane B. (Box 61)
  - Allen, Elizabeth (Box 61)
  - Allen, Gertrude H. (Box 61)
  - Allen, Margaret S. (Box 61)
  - Ames, Adelaide (Box 61)
  - Andrews, Jane C. (Box 61)
  - Arnold, Alice (Box 61)
  - Askew, Mary E. (Box 61)
  - Atlass, Beatrice (Box 61)
  - Averill, Dorothy B. (Box 61)
  - Avery, Onnollee, S. (Box 61)
  - Ayer, Caroline E. (Box 61)
  - Bacon, Frances (Box 61)
  - Bacon, Marion (Box 61)
  - Baldwin, Charlotte (Box 61)
  - Baldwin, Ruth E. (Box 61)
  - Ball, Elisabeth (Box 61)
  - Banister, Marion E. (Box 61)
  - DeM Barbey, Constance (Box 61)
  - Barclay, Bertha F. (Box 61)
  - Barmon, Helen L. (Box 61)
  - Barney, Sarah B. (Box 61)
  - Barritt, Vivian R. (Box 61)
  - Bartlett, Genevieve R. (Box 61)
  - Beard, Miriam (Box 61)
  - Beatty, Helen H. (Box 61)
  - Beavers, Geraldine L. (Box 61)
  - Beck, Elsa C. (Box 61)
  - Beede, Faustina K. (Box 61)
  - Bennett, Madeleine D. (Box 61)
  - Bill, Elizabeth H. (Box 61)
  - Billings, Katharine H. (Box 61)
  - Bishoff, Helen M. (Box 61)
  - Bishop, Eleanor (Box 61)
  - Bliss, Margaret (Box 61)
  - Booraem, E. Dorothy (Box 61)
  - Born, Marian S. (Box 61)
  - Borton, Faith (Box 61)
  - Brandt, Elizabeth M. (Box 61)
  - Bridgman, Harriet (Box 61)
  - Brill, Edith C. (Box 61)
  - Bronson, Geraldine M. (Box 61)
  - Brown, Elizabeth G. (Box 61)
  - Brown, Susan B. (Box 61)
  - Bruce, May H. (Box 61)
  - Budd, Dorothy (Box 61)
  - Burdick, Mary S. (Box 61)
  - Burr, Helen M. (Box 61)
  - Bushnell, Marjorie R. (Box 61)
  - Butler, Henrietta A. (Box 61)
  - Buzzell, Madeline C. (Box 61)
  - Card, Katherine B. (Box 61)
  - Card, Mary F. (Box 61)
  - Carpenter, Charlotte M. (Box 61)
  - Chapman, Edith M. (Box 61)
  - Chatfield, Constance (Box 61)
  - Childs, A. Muriel (Box 61)
  - Clifford, Gretchen (Box 61)
  - Clinton, Helen (Box 61)
  - Colby, H. Louise (Box 61)
  - Cowles, Harriet (Box 61)
  - Cox, Katharine E. (Box 61)
  - Crofoot, Virginia (Box 61)
  - Cummings, Ruth D. (Box 61)
  - Currier, Edith S. (Box 61)
  - Dern, Mary J. (Box 61)
  - Derr, Katharine (Box 61)
  - Doan, Miriam (Box 61)
  - Doble, Alice M. (Box 61)
  - Doskova, Mary (Box 61)
  - Doughten, Marie L. (Box 61)
  - Douglas, Deborah L. (Box 61)
  - Downer, Dorothy (Box 61)
  - Drislane, Genevieve E. (Box 61)
  - Edwards, Sarah Charline -EMPTY (Box 61)
  - Eicher, Sara K. (Box 61)
  - Embery, Mabel (Box 61)
  - Esselstyn, Mary S. (Box 61)
  - Esty, Frances F. (Box 61)
  - Evans, Elizabeth (Box 61)
  - Farrar, Margaret (Box 61)
  - Fay, Caroline J. (Box 61)
  - Fay, Mildred E. (Box 61)
  - Field, Ruth (Box 61)
  - Fifield, Elizabeth S. (Box 61)
  - Fine, Margaret B. (Box 61)
  - Fiske, Madeline (Box 61)
  - Fitch, Edith S. (Box 61)
  - Flanagan, Alice M. (Box 61)
  - Folwell, Helen M. (Box 61)
  - Ford, Jean H. (Box 61)
  - Foster, Evelyn L. (Box 61)
  - Foster, Jane Louise, [EMPTY] (Box 61)
  - Fowler, Janet (Box 61)
  - Fox, Dorothy E., [EMPTY] (Box 61)
  - Fox, Grace E. (Box 61)
  - Frank, Mary (Box 61)
  - Franke, Virginia E. (Box 61)
  - Freeland, Lucie W. (Box 61)
  - Rita Fuguet (Box 61)
  - Gaston, Mary M. (Box 61)
  - Gehring, Hulda (Box 61)
  - Gilbert, Elizabeth (Box 61)
  - Gilhooly, Marjorie (Box 61)
  - Glasgow, Elizabeth A. (Box 61)
  - Goldsmith, Ruth V., [EMPTY] (Box 61)
  - Goodkind, Ruth (Box 61)
  - Graham, Janet (Box 61)
  - Gratz, Helen, [EMPTY] (Box 61)
  - Greene, Helen (Box 61)
  - Grier, Harriet E. (Box 61)
  - Groce, Annette S. (Box 61)
  - Guy, Evelyn S. - EMPTY (Box 61)
  - Haines, E. Marian (Box 62)
  - Halliday, Mary H. (Box 62)
  - Halsey, Cortenay W. (Box 62)
  - Hamilton, Allegra E. (Box 62)
  - Hanna, Katharine (Box 62)
  - Harrison, Acile (Box 62)
  - Hartman, Sarah C. (Box 62)
  - Hartwell, Frances (Box 62)
  - Hartwell, Madeleine (Box 62)
  - Haskins, Ruth F. (Box 62)
  - Hastings, L. Ahnawake (Box 62)
  - Hatt, Elise (Box 62)
  - Hawes, Charlotte A. (Box 62)
  - Hawes, Marian A., [EMPTY] (Box 62)
  - Haynes, Emily L. (Box 62)
  - Hays, Ethel S. (Box 62)
  - Healy, Grace (Box 62)
  - Herrick, Ruth T. (Box 62)
  - Hicks, Harriet W. (Box 62)
  - Higgins, Jeannette L. (Box 62)
  - Higgins, Rachel (Box 62)
  - Hiteman, Dorothy L. (Box 62)
  - Hodges, Lucy S. (Box 62)
  - Holcombe, M. Louise (Box 62)
  - Hollard, Mireille C. (Box 62)
  - Hollister, Gloria E. (Box 62)
  - Holt, Elizabeth B. (Box 62)
  - Holway, Mary L. (Box 62)
  - Hopkins, Rosamonde A. (Box 62)
  - Hopkins, Sally M. (Box 62)
  - Howe, Mary (Box 62)
  - Huling, Elizabeth (Box 62)
  - Hull, Mary C. (Box 62)
  - Hunley, Dorothy (Box 62)
  - Hurley, Julia (Box 62)
  - Hurst, Mary S. (Box 62)
  - Hussey, Miriam (Box 62)
  - Huston, Gladys A., [EMPTY] (Box 62)
  - Hutton, Josephine (Box 62)
  - Hyde, Ruth V. (Box 62)
  - Jackson, Helen W. (Box 62)
  - Janes, Frances B. (Box 62)
  - Jarasse, Emilie A. (Box 62)
  - Jeanne, Helen A. (Box 62)
  - Jenison, Judith (Box 62)
  - Johnson, Abigail A. (Box 62)
  - Johnson, Dorothy V. (Box 62)
  - Johnson, Margaret (Box 62)
  - Johnson, Marian (Box 62)
  - Johnson, Miriam (Box 62)
  - Jones, Margaret L. (Box 62)
  - Keiser, Martha E. (Box 62)
  - Kelly, Harriet R. - EMPTY (Box 62)
  - Kepler, Dorothy F. (Box 62)
  - Kerley, Barbara (Box 62)
  - Kernan, Katharine (Box 62)
  - Kilpatrick, Mary Lydston (Box 62)
  - King, Helen B. (Box 62)
  - Kittredge, Edwina (Box 62)
  - Knisely, Margaret Gould (Box 62)
  - Koenig, Gertrude A. (Box 62)
  - Langthorn, Jane A. (Box 62)
  - Laws, Dorothy B. (Box 62)
  - Lea, Elise F. (Box 62)
  - Lee, E. Bruce (Box 62)
  - Leonard, Ada H. (Box 62)
  - Lewis, Jane N. (Box 62)
  - Lewis, Millicent H. (Box 62)
  - Lichty, Ruth (Box 62)
  - Link, Elisabeth M. (Box 62)
  - Loewenthal, Juliet R. (Box 62)
  - Long, Lois (Box 62)
  - Loomis, Catherine N. (Box 62)
  - Loy, Gladys M., [EMPTY] (Box 62)
  - Ludington, Dorothy A. (Box 62)
  - Lyon, Doreen (Box 62)
  - Lyon, Mary P. (Box 62)
  - Lytle, Laura W. (Box 62)
  - MacGregor, Helen M. (Box 62)
  - MacLaughlin, Helene L. (Box 62)
  - Magennis, Mary E. (Box 62)
  - Maisel, Ida S. (Box 62)
  - Malven, Jean (Box 62)
  - Mann, Eleanor N. (Box 62)
  - Manning, S. Elizabeth (Box 62)
  - Mathews, Elizabeth A. (Box 62)
  - Matouskova, Julia (Box 62)
  - May, Jean B. (Box 62)
  - Mayo, Edith (Box 62)
  - McCarthy, Helen M. (Box 62)
  - McConway, Louise (Box 62)
  - McCormick, Emily F. (Box 62)
  - McGiffert, Mary Y. (Box 62)
  - McClean, Jean (Box 62)
  - McMakin, Theresa W. (Box 62)
  - McReynolds, Mary V. (Box 62)
  - Metzger, Louise, [EMPTY] (Box 62)
  - Meyers, Marian F. (Box 62)
  - Miller, Evelyn, [EMPTY] (Box 62)
  - Milliken, Margaret F. (Box 62)
  - Morris, Christine (Box 62)
  - Morris, Louise (Box 62)
  - Morrison, Edith G. (Box 62)
  - Morse, Elizabeth (Box 62)
  - Moseley, Mary H. (Box 62)
  - Mott, Irene (Box 62)
  - Mulvaney, Helen (Box 62)
  - Neff, Dorothy I. (Box 62)
  - Neff, Gladys (Box 62)
  - Neff, Margaret B. (Box 62)
  - Nichols, Dorothy E., [EMPTY] (Box 62)
  - Nicolet, Frances S. (Box 62)
  - Norwood, Mildred (Box 62)
  - Novakova, Marie (Box 62)
  - Oberlaender, A. Dorothy (Box 62)
  - Oppenheim, Julia (Box 62)
  - Otto, Charlotte (Box 62)
  - Owens, Olga van Slyke (Box 62)
  - Parrott, Dorothy A. (Box 62)
  - Parsons, Elizabeth J. (Box 62)
  - Pearson, Dorothy L. (Box 62)
  - Penny, Elizabeth B. (Box 62)